{	"div":
	[	
		{
			"Problem":"58.2/0.3",
			"answer":"58.2/0.3",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"5.34/0.6",
			"answer":"5.34/0.6",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"0.051/0.03",
			"answer":"0.051/0.03",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"300/0.002",
			"answer":"300/0.002",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"8.37/0.3",
			"answer":"8.37/0.3",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"11.2/0.08",
			"answer":"11.2/0.08",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"0.942/0.6",
			"answer":"0.942/0.6",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"240/0.008",
			"answer":"240/0.008",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"0.094/0.2",
			"answer":"0.094/0.2",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"60.6/0.02",
			"answer":"60.6/0.02",
			"status":"unsolved"
		}
	]
}